仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.ZiMuZu.tv
原创翻译  双语字幕
翻译:  冰蓝    glida     洗七里
翻译:  MsFool    小泡椒    芝小士
校对:  以帅谋私赛太公
时间轴:  三水
后期:  瓜瓜    总监： 怀念浓子的瓜瓜
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    美剧炸了
了解最新影视资讯字幕信息
摩  登
家  庭
第八季 第八集
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
手机APP搜索
人人影视字幕组
打开微信
扫描左侧二维码
关注凤凰八卦
意大利千层面早餐
Ahh, breakfast lasagna!
很棒的决定  亲爱的
Great call, honey.
离它远点
Stay away from it.
这是给大家今晚吃的
It's for everybody tonight.
还得等两餐呢
That's two meals away.
喂
Hello.
上校  怎么了
Hey, Colonel, what's up?
妈咪  伊凡能来吃晚餐吗
Mommy, could Ivan come for dinner?
不行  先生
No, senor,
因为今晚全家人
'cause tonight the whole family
都会来吃晚餐
is coming over for dinner,
因为我们要投票决定
'cause we're gonna vote on
我们今年要去哪里度假
where we're going on vacation this year.
一场由道德污点的投票
A vote with a moral stain on it,
只有拥有土地的成年人才有投票权
since ballots are reserved for land-owning adults.
因为没人想去
Because nobody wants to go
小说家埃德加·爱伦·坡的出生地
to the birthplace of Edgar Allan Poe.
该死的上校害死我了
Damn Colonel screwed me
撤回我请愿书上他的名字
and took his name off my petition.
我想废除俱乐部通过的愚蠢规定
I'm trying to overturn this dumb rule the club passed
在正厅40英尺范围内禁止抽雪茄
banning cigars within 40 feet of the main lodge.
我的国家通过
When my country passed a law
一项允许人民淹死14岁的孩子的法律时
that allowed them to drown 14 year olds,
你说"这种事时有发生"
you said, "These things happen."
我刚买了一盒征服者特别雪茄
I just bought a box of El Conquistador Especiales.
它们应该被人坐在上等皮椅上抽
And they deserve to be smoked in a fine leather chair,
而不是在蜘蛛满地爬区域的喷泉旁边抽
not out by the fountain in some heavily-spidered area.
我不希望家里有这个
I don't want this in my house.
在家没法抽  在俱乐部没法抽
Can't smoke at home, can't smoke at the club.
也许斯黛拉的狗窝里有地方
Maybe Stella has room in her doghouse.
她在哪里
Where is she, anyway?
从早上开始就没见她了
Haven't seen her since the morning.
我不知道斯黛拉在哪里
I don't know where Stella is.
我觉得这跟
I think it has something to do
我不得不给她戴的电击项圈有关
with the shock collar that I had to put on her
因为她整天乱往外跑
because she kept running away.
也许我可以告诉杰  我以为那是条项链
Maybe I tell Jay that I thought it was a necklace.
他自己可是也想过给她打耳洞呢
He was the one who wanted to pierce her ears.
亲爱的  你的早餐在桌上了
Hey sweetie, your breakfast is on the table.
这是什么
Ah, what's this?
让我猜猜
Oh! Ooh, let me guess.
古龙香水广告里的人吗
The guy in the cologne ad.
我给意大利帅哥取了名  叫乔瓦尼
I've named him. It's Giovanni.
他爱上了我
He's in love with me.
他要为了我离开你
Well, he's leaving you for me.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我们不想这样的
We never meant for it to happen.
那是什么
What's that?
-是吐司做好了  -租了楼上房间的
- Toast, toast is done. - Those Russian brothers
俄罗斯兄弟
who are renting the unit upstairs,
-他们  -走了
- are they... - Gone.
因为已经到了30天
Because it's already been 30 days, okay?
规定很清楚
And the rules are very clear.
我知道占屋者权  米奇尔
I know all about squatter's rights, Mitchell.
又称不动产权  美国部分州可以合法占屋子
占够久还能变业主
你为什么总是得把我当做
Why do you always have to treat me
不负责任的...
like I'm some irresponsible...
蠢货
Idiot?
俄罗斯兄弟还想住一晚
The Russian brothers wanted one more night.
所以我收了现金  没告诉米奇尔
So I took cash, and I didn't tell Mitchell,
现在他们不肯走了
and now they won't leave.
我们碰到了非法占屋者
We have squatters.
一开始是白蚁  现在是非法占屋者
First termites, now squatters.
至少入侵的白蚁不是我的错
At least the termites weren't my fault.
瞧瞧这美丽的小桌
Look at this beautiful side table
有人把它丢到了街上
somebody just left on the street.
-需要帮忙吗  -不用  这个小桌轻到莫名其妙
- Oh, do you need a hand? - No, it's like ridiculously light.
给我爱人[意语]的煎饼
Flapjacks for mi amore?
-谢谢[意语]  -我不知道什么更甜如糖浆
- Oh, grazie. - Ugh. I don't know what's more syrupy --
你俩还是卢克的下巴
you two or Luke's chin.
真奇怪  我还没吃早餐呢
That's weird. I haven't had breakfast yet.
很抱歉
You'll have to excuse us.
你爸爸和我
Your father and I watched
昨晚看了一部很浪漫的电影
a very romantic movie last night.
好  谷歌
Okay, Google,
播放《给佩佩的意面》的原声音乐
play the soundtrack to "Spaghetti for Pepe."
播放中
Playing soundtrack.
抱歉
Ooh. Mi scusa.
-看着点新鞋  -什么
- Whoa. Watch the new kicks. - What?
你又买了一双新运动鞋吗
You have another pair of new sneakers?
俱乐部的工作薪水多少啊
What is that job at the club paying you?
是小费  妈妈
It's the tips, mom.
有位女士
There's this one lady,
帮她扶着门  十块
hold the door for her -- 10 bucks.
端给她一杯柠檬冰茶  又是十块
Bring her an ice tea with lemon, another 10 bucks.
我拿过的最多小费是
Best tips I ever made was when we passed the hat
我的即兴表演团队"三法则"表演募捐到的
after a performance of my improv group, "Rule of Three."
我们以小品  搞笑改编歌曲
We were known for our sketches, song parodies,
和正面全裸闻名
and full-frontal nudity.
喂
Hello?
你们都没有橙汁了
You are all out of orange juice.
我懂了
I understand.
我得出去买橙汁了
I have to go out for orange juice.
我懂了
Yes, I understand.
我得出去买橙汁了
I have to go out for orange juice.
米奇尔
Mitchell?
我得出去买橙汁了
I have to go out for orange juice.
谢谢你们过来  我跟俄罗斯人之间出了问题
Thank you for coming. I have a problem with Russians.
跟普里契特家族的人结婚挺好的
Being married to a Pritchett is great.
-非常好  -太棒了
- So great! - The best!
但他们有点爱批评
But they can be a -- a tad judgmental.
-简直是惩罚  -他们是禽兽
- Almost punitive. - They are monsters.
所以我们三个人组建了秘密同盟
That's why the three of us formed a -- a secret alliance
来掩护彼此之间的
to help each other cover up our --
-小错误  -比如去年十二月的时候
- our little mistakes. - Like back in December,
我一时冲动为开放日乱买了一个
when I hastily purchased an expensive prop
昂贵的道具
for an open house.
非常感谢你帮忙我藏它
Thanks so much for hiding it.
克莱尔会杀了我的
Claire would kill me.
等到周一我就能退掉了
And it's only till Monday, when I can return it.
别担心
Don't worry.
欢迎回家
Oh, welcome home!
-你回来得真早啊  -没有吧
- You're so early, right? - Not really.
我就爱你这样的笑容
There is that smile that I love.
-你带我出去共进午餐吧  -好
- Why don't you take me to lunch? - Okay.
到底是什么情况
What happened here, anyway?
你又吸乔的香味马克笔吸嗨了吗
You get into Joe's scented markers again?
所以现在有可怕的俄国人在我家赖着不肯走
So now, I have scary Russian squatters who won't leave.
等米奇尔去健身房  我们就有一小段时间
We'll have a small window when Mitchell goes to the gym.
他通常会做做伸展运动  在更衣室溜一圈
He usually stretches, takes a lap around the locker room,
然后喝杯奶昔
and then gets a smoothie.
你们俩负责那些俄国人
You two deal with the Russians,
我来转移米奇注意
and I'll keep Mitch distracted.
-还有事吗  -有
- Anything else? - Yes.
我们家门坏了
Our gate is broken,
斯黛拉不停跑到街上去
and Stella keeps getting out in the street.
我给它买了一个电击项圈
I bought her a shock collar.
卢克小时候我也想过买一个
I thought about getting one when Luke was younger.
结果克莱尔靠对他摇零钱罐让他乖乖过来
Claire ended up just shaking a can of pennies at him.
它被吓到  躲了起来
It spooked her and she's hiding.
我们得在杰之前找到它  免得杰看到项圈
We need to find her before Jay does and sees the collar.
他多次警告我不要买
He has warned me many times not to get one
因为那很残忍
because they are cruel.
好  我们先解决俄国人
All right, we'll deal with the Russians first,
然后在投票前找到斯黛拉
then come find Stella before the big vote.
我们时间不多
We do not have much time.
得行动了
We need to go.
其实我点了三明治
I actually ordered a sandwich.
雷纳还没来吗
Is Rainer not here yet?
不  他来了
Oh no, he is.
我都没要  他就给我签了张大头照
He, uh, signed a head shot I didn't ask for,
然后去了洗手间
and then went to the bathroom.
那是他女儿
There's his daughter.
我从未认识过男友的女儿
I've never met a boyfriend's daughter before.
虽然我和史黛西的老爸约会过
I mean, I went out with Stacy's dad,
但我从幼儿园就认识她了
but I've known her since, like, kindergarten.
你紧张吗
You're nervous?
这还能出什么岔子
I mean, how could this go wrong?
她是青少女  而你人生巅峰就是在那段期间
She's a teenage girl. That's when you peaked.
我知道
I know.
大概我真的很喜欢他
I guess I just really like this guy,
我想让他看到
and I want to be able to show him
我能融入他生活中最复杂的部分
I can fit into the more complicated parts of his life.
小公主
Hey, princess.
六个人拍我跟女交警争论
Six people filmed me arguing with that meter maid,
却没人拍到这美秒的时刻吗
and no one caught this adorable moment?
你肯定就是艾普丽了
So, you must be April.
废话
Uh, yeah?
艾普丽  注意语气
April, tone.
我搬个椅子过来
I'll grab a chair.
抱歉  工作电话  必须得接
Sorry. That's work. Gotta take that.
总之  我是海莉  你爸的...
Anyways, I'm Haley, your dad's, uh --
-最新一任  -太好了
- Latest? - Yes!
莫哈维突发洪水  需要我去报道
Flash flood in the Mohave, they need me to cover.
老年中心水已经上升到坡道
The water's already ramp high at the senior center.
一只小狗乘着披萨盒漂过
You know, a puppy floats by on a pizza box,
这报道可能轰动全国
this could be national.
糟了  我们今天的安排怎么办
Oops, snakes. Our day!
我可以去妈和杰夫那里
I'll just go to mom and Jeff's.
别别  我们今天本该互相认识一下的
No, no, we were supposed to get to know each other today.
我能看着你
Um, I can watch you.
因为我四岁吗
Because I'm 4?
注意语气
Oh, tone.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
当然  我们俩女孩一起玩  晚点见
Yes. Girls day. We'll meet you later.
好  谢谢你的理解  宝贝
Oh, okay, thank you for understanding, sweetie.
-没什么  -没什么
- No problem. - No problem.
灾难袭来
Tragedy strikes.
数十人死亡
Dozens dead.
灾难袭来
Tragedy strikes.
数十人死亡
Dozens dead.
我们最后一项议程是
And our final order of business is
参加今年的国际衣橱博览会
our entry to this year's Expo Internacional du Closet.
有什么提议
What do we got?
我们都知道
Okay, so we all know
欧洲人喜欢有力又简单的线条
that Europeans prefer strong but simple lines...
所以我认为我们应该选择特拉法加
which is why I think that we should go with the Trafalgar.
有点意思
Interesting.
坚实又可靠
It's sturdy, dependable.
另一方面
On the other hand,
马特洪峰可能会是颠覆性的选择
the Matterhorn is a chance to shake things up.
想想02年丹麦人的成绩
Think about what the Danes did in '02.
也有道理
Also valid.
大胆而创新
It's bold, innovative.
我得接个电话
Ah, gotta take this.
俱乐部的民权问题  我得处理
Civil rights issue over at the club I have to deal with.
你好
Hello.
有什么好笑的
What's so funny?
你们在笑什么
What are you laughing at?
你第一次参展这么紧张很可爱
It's so cute how nervous you are about your first expo.
每次我们提出个想法
It's like every time we throw out an idea,
你都得看你爸是怎么想的
you have to look to see what your dad is thinking.
我才没有
I don't do that.
我完全没有那样  多米
I-I-I don't do that at all, Dom.
或许你对你爸是那样
Maybe you do that with your dad.
盖里非要我签他的请愿书才会签我的
Gary won't sign my petition unless I sign his.
除非火焰地狱变成酷寒极地
It'll be a cold day in hell before that
否则他别想穿人字拖打高尔夫
hippie tees off in flip-flops.
我们谈到哪了
Where were we?
我正在纠结该选择
I was just about to make my decision
特拉法加  还是马特洪峰
between the Trafalgar and the Matterhorn.
我身着帅气西服  有最赞的办公室
I got the power suit, the corner office.
这城市所安装的任何新衣柜
A closet doesn't get installed in this town
都得本后知情了才能开工
without me knowing about it.
但一碰上重要的决定
But one important decision,
突然间  我就变成穿小皮鞋头顶小辫
and suddenly I'm this pig-tailed little girl in Mary Janes
渴望被爸爸夸奖聪明的小女孩了
looking to daddy to tell me I'm smart.
现在做这重要的决定有些为时过早
Uh, it's...too important a decision to make right now.
我还是多花点时间考虑一下吧
I'm just gonna take the rest of the day to think about it.
但必须在五点前回复慕尼黑
Okay, but Munich needs to know by 5:00.
我知道  但这是个艰难的选择
I know, but this is a tough choice.
是吗
Is it?
我带了你今晚的衣服来
Hey, I brought your clothes for tonight.
谢谢  亲爱的  你真是贴心小棉袄
Oh, thank you honey, that's so sweet.
-事情怎么样...  -无线网登不上
- How's it going with, um... - The wi-fi won't work,
而且这地方闻起来全是方便面味儿
and this whole place smells like Cup O' Noodles.
妈妈  这是艾普丽  雷纳的女儿
Mom, this is April, Rainer's daughter.
-很高兴见到你  -你好
- Pleasure to meet you. - Hi.
我想去下洗手间
So, I'm gonna look for a ladies' room.
工厂里有洗手间吗
Do they have those in factories?
有的  走廊尽头就是
Uh, we do, yes. It's just down the hall.
走廊尽头就是
Just down the hall.
谢谢啊  应声虫
Thanks, echo.
你笑什么
What's so funny?
看你得管着一个青少女觉得好笑
Oh, just you dealing with a teenage girl.
没想象中那么简单吧
Not as easy as it looks, is it?
不好意思  我管得可好了
Excuse me. I'm doing just fine.
好啊  孩子们
Hey, kiddo.
今晚重要的假期投票你来吗
We gonna see you tonight for the big vacation vote?
那当然  介意我带个烦死人的青少女吗
You bet. Mind if I bring an unbearable teenager?
多一个又何妨
What's one more.
听着  我要去俱乐部一趟
Listen, I'm gonna run over to the club
为我的雪茄请愿书凑到最后一个签名
and scare up one last signature for my cigar petition.
你决定好选哪个衣柜参加博览会了吗
Oh, have you decided on what closet for the expo?
因为我在想...
'Cause I was thinking --
不不不  不用了  谢谢
No! No, no, no. No, thank you.
我做好决定时  一定会告知你的
I will let you know when I have made my decision.
没问题  三明治看起来挺好吃
Sure. Sandwich looks good.
是吗  你觉得挺好吃吗
Does it? Does it look good to you?
你觉得不意味就真的好吃
'Cause that doesn't mean it's a good sandwich.
没错  这三明治一点也不好吃
It's not. As a matter of fact, it's not a good sandwich.
好吧  大家今晚见
All right, see you guys later tonight.
-你就捡回来吧  -好的
- Just do it. - Okay.
卢克
Luke?
小家伙
Buddy?
凯文  刚上那上车的是不是我孙子
Kevin, was that my grandson taking off in that sportscar?
是啊  没错
Yeah, it was.
你这么贼兮兮地回答  到底怎么回事
That's quite a spin on that response. What's going on?
玛吉·布雷斯韦特派给了他一些她家里的活
Maggie Braithwait has some work for him to do around her house.
她比较中意小鲜肉
She's got an eye for the young ones.
我该担心吗
Should I be worried?
她也许会尝试对他下手
She might try and pressure him a little,
但卢克是个聪明孩子  对吗
but Luke's a smart kid, right?
我靠
Damn it.
谢天谢地你来了
Oh, thank God you're here.
我能听见楼上的俄国人嘲笑民主政治
I can hear the Russians upstairs laughing at democracy.
-我们一起上去吧  -不  我单独行动
- All right, shall we? - No. I work alone.
如果你听见两声身体撞地  就是解决了
If you hear two bodies hit the floor, it's done.
要是听见第三声  就赶紧找后援
If you hear three, one tried to get back up.
好吧
Okay...
真对不起
I'm so sorry!
菲尔
Phil!
米奇尔
Mitchell!
真是巧啊  你来这家健身房健身吗
Wow, that's crazy. Is -- is this your gym?
没错
Yeah.
我正准备去邮局呢
I was just heading into the post office.
你介意陪我一起吗  他们办事很快的
You mind keeping me company? They're always quick.
其实呢  我要去...
Oh, well, actually, I gotta --
我的钥匙不见了
I don't have my keys.
我一定是丢哪里了
Oh, I must have dropped them.
真糟糕  我可以帮你到健身房找找
Oh, no. Well, I'll -- I'll help you check the gym.
你还记得用过哪些健身器材吗
You remember what machines you were using?
全部
All of them.
我们搜索遍了整个健身房
We scoured that gym.
其实还真花了相当长的时间
It actually did take a crazy long time,
因为米奇尔一直迷路
because Mitchell kept getting lost.
但我还需要再拖延一会儿
But I still needed a little more time.
抱歉耽误了你这么久
Sorry that took so long.
一碰上图书馆旧书清仓我就走不动道
I can't pass up a library book sale.
只要一美元就能买到塞满车后箱的杂志
I mean, a dollar for as many magazines as you can fit in the car.
没错  《国家地理》
Yeah, National Geo--
《爱尔兰  蛮夷的土地》
Ireland: Land of Savages.
这事多少年前出版的啊
How old are these?
-你好  亲爱的  -菲尔
- Hi, honey. - Hey, Phil,
我知道今早你已经去过超市买橙汁了
I know you already went to the store for O.J. This morning,
但你回来路上能再去买点红酒晚上喝吗
but can you go back and grab some wine for tonight?
没问题  再见  美女
You got it. Ciao, bella.
你今早去买橙汁了吗
You went out for orange juice this morning?
真巧  小卡也是
That's a coincidence. Cam did too.
的确是巧  那...  那真是
That is a coincidence. That's -- that's really...
你好
有何贵干
每天我都会带乔去一个在俄罗斯社区的公园
Every day, I take Joe to a park in a Russian neighborhood.
我们很喜欢去那里
We like it there.
那些俄国保姆管教俄国娃时
I have picked up a few phrases
我学会了一些俄语短语
that the Russian nannies tell to the Russian kids.
游戏时间结束了
你谁
你们两个坏小子  到该回家的时候了
你觉得她是真有来头吗
长这么漂亮还会说俄语的女人肯定有后台
和朋友们说再见吧  到小睡的时间了
她肯定认识"屠夫"
我很肯定咱们能把事情商量妥的
难道你们想尝尝炸鸡柳的滋味吗
女王饶命  别把我的手炸成鸡柳
其实很简单的  米奇
Well, it's pretty simple, Mitch.
你只要乱摸一通
You just touch everything,
等开拖车的人来了
and then when the tow truck guy shows up
看到你满手油污就会觉得你是行家
and sees your dirty paws, he knows you're a pro.
还要尽可能多说"风扇传动皮带"
Also, say "fan belt" as often as you...
米奇尔
Mitchell?
是我
Hello.
红熊猫已逃离动物园
The red panda's left the zoo.
-什么红熊猫  -米奇尔的代号
- Red panda? - Mitchell's code name!
我已经尽可能拖住他了  还是被他跑了
I stalled him for as long as I could, and he got away.
-那我还有多少时间  -我也不知道
- Okay, well, how much time do I have? - I'm not sure.
我都不知道我现在在哪
I don't really know where I am.
我只能看见
All I can see is --
-原来就在你家旁边  -什么
- Oh, there's your house. - What?
-小卡  -回来啦  甜心
- Cam. - Hi, sweetheart!
少用你那套《乱世佳人》的南方风情迷惑我
Save the Southern charm, Scarlett.
-菲尔明显是想阻止我回家来  -什么
- Phil was clearly just trying to keep me from here. - What?
我先是丢了钥匙
Yeah, I-I lost my keys,
然后他就突然出现
and sudden-suddenly he shows up and --
这是不是和我们早上听到的
Does this have something to do
楼上传来的撞击声有什么关系
with the thud we heard upstairs?
米奇尔  我这话是带着爱意说的
Mitchell, I-I say this with love,
但你这是纯脑子抽风啊
but you're coming unhinged.
你对我的这些怀疑  这些指控
The suspicions, the accusations,
滚床单时机械化的表现
the mechanical sexual performance --
我心爱的米奇尔哪去了
Where has Mitchell gone?
但我又不是医生
Yeah, I'm -- but I'm not a doctor,
所以你要是非说楼上有事情不对
so if you think something's going on upstairs,
那咱务必上去看个清楚
by all means, let's go take a look.
可话说回来
You know, on the other hand,
假如我是名医生  我会说
if I were a doctor, I would say,
"你编出这么多阴谋论是怎么回事"
"What's up with all the conspiracy theories?"
你这是教科书般的偏执狂啊
It's textbook paranoia.
人人都这么说
Everyone's talking about it.
但话又说回来  我不是医生
But again, not a doctor,
咱这就上楼吧
so shall we?
你知道在俄语里
Well, you know, there are 30 different ways
有30种方式说"对不起"吗
to say "I'm sorry" in Russian.
对不起
I'm sorry.
或许的确是我多疑了
Maybe I was being paranoid.
我接受你的道歉
Apology accepted,
我也很抱歉我说你床上技巧机械化
and I'm sorry for calling your lovemaking mechanical.
我其实很喜欢你那个害羞教师的角色扮演
I actually really like your shy, school teacher character.
征服者特别雪茄
El Conquistador Especial.
我爸抽的牌子
My dad's brand.
但我不明白上面为什么会有唇膏
That doesn't explain the lipstick, though.
我爸连润唇膏都不肯用
No, my dad won't even wear Chapstick.
他说爷们擦多了会变基
He says it's a gateway balm.
-外公  -我天
- Grandpa? - Oh, geez.
我就知道我应该闯那个黄灯来阻止
I knew I should have run that yellow.
你上衣呢
Where's your shirt?
布雷斯韦特女士想让我搬几个箱子
Mrs. Braithwait wanted me to move some boxes,
她叫我脱掉上衣以免弄脏衣服
and told me to take it off so it didn't get dirty.
但我还是觉得自己变得"肮脏"了
But I kinda feel dirty anyway.
去拿衣服  我们这就走
Grab your shirt. We're leaving.
卢克  把你那条脏脏的紧身裤脱下来洗洗吧
Luke, let's get those dirty, tight pants in the wash.
幸会
Oh, hello.
你好
How are ya?
我是来接我刚满18岁的外孙的
I'm here to pick up my barely-legal grandson.
我认得你
I recognize you.
你也是俱乐部的  对吧
From the club, right?
你就是那反抗新的白痴禁雪茄令的家伙
You're the one fighting that silly new cigar rule.
不好意思  你把我上衣放哪了
Excuse me? Where'd you put my shirt?
让我们单独聊聊  孩子
Give us a minute, kid.
那条禁雪茄令的确很蠢  不是吗
It is a dumb rule, isn't it?
蠢到家了
It's terrible.
我已故的前夫最爱在正厅里抽了
My late husband loved smoking in the main lodge.
你逼我喷的古龙水就是他的吗
Is that whose cologne you made me put on?
行了行了  你不是还有箱子要搬吗
Hey, hey, hey. Boxes, right?
我这里有份请愿书
I've got a petition here.
不如你瞟一眼
Why don't you read it quick?
你没准愿意签名呢
You might want to sign it.
我觉得现在可能不是时候
Oh, I'm not sure now's such a good time.
我这脖子
My neck is so...
卢克  还不伺候着
Luke, get in there.
施展一下你双手的魔力
Put your magic fingers to work.
你怎么这么了解我身体的需求
Mm. How do you know my body this well?
就签在那个X上
Right there on the "X."
你看起来够放松了
Oh, you seem relaxed.
我该停手了
I should stop.
再揉一会儿
Not just yet.
为了方便您
If it would be easier,
您握着笔就好
just hold the pen,
我来帮您挪纸
and I will move the paper underneath.
我要是知道你手法这么好
If I'd have known you were this good,
我就让你帮我揉脚了
I would have had you do my feet.
他会揉到脚的
He's gonna get there.
他会从头揉到脚的
He's working his way down.
或许只签个缩写就够了
Probably just your initials would be okay.
你猜怎么着
You know what?
你要是不介意的话我想晚点再签
If you don't mind, I'm gonna sign this later,
和卢克一起给你送回家去
send it home with Luke.
行了  走你的吧
All right, come on.
我们完事了
We're done.
好的  不过
Okay, but, uh...
你一定会签字的吧
...you're definitely gonna sign it, right?
一定  我保证
Definitely, promise.
再见
Bye-bye.
卢克  我们差不多该上楼
Luke, we should probably get upstairs
把床垫翻个面了
and flip that mattress.
卢克  不好意思啊
Luke, I'm sorry.
我忘了你妈
I forgot your mom
喊你回家上钢琴课
needs you home for your piano lesson.
-我们走吧  -我要走了  回见
- Let's go. - Gotta run. See ya.
你反应得也太慢了
Took you long enough.
得了吧  不过慢了10秒钟
Oh, please, it was an extra 10 seconds.
能出什么事
What could have happened?
她一边让我做引体向上
She asked me to do push-ups
一边穿上她的婚纱
while she put on her wedding dress.
她直接跳到婚礼后无力入洞房的戏码了吗
Wow, she jumped right to the Honeymoon Handshake.
这招还有名字啊
It has a name?
你跟你爸从来不聊天吗
Don't you and your dad ever talk?
-我们到处找了斯黛拉  找不到  -目前还没有
- Okay, we've searched everywhere for Stella, no sign. - Yet.
别急  我们会在灰山羊之前找到她的
Don't worry, we'll find her before the gray goat does.
谁
Who?
就是杰  伙伴们长点心
Jay. Come on, guys,
我花了很多时间一直在说那些代号
I spend a lot of time on those code names.
好吧  快一点  因为他要给她拍照
Okay, hurry, because he takes a picture of her
在每一天的同一时刻拍
every day at the same time
因为他要做一个翻书动画
because he's making a flip book.
注意  注意
Ay, watch out, watch out.
我觉得米奇尔在看我们
I think Mitchell is looking at us.
我以为今天早上我已经解除了他的疑心
Okay, I thought I cooled his suspicions this morning.
大笑然后散开
Laugh and disperse.
-妈妈  喝红酒吗  -谢谢
- Hey, mom. Red wine? - Oh, thanks.
-外公说你会喜欢的  -真的吗
- Grandpa said you'd like it. - Really?
谁在乎他怎么想
Well, who cares what he thinks?
他喜欢什么  我就应该也喜欢吗
Just 'cause he likes something, I'm supposed to like it?
不现实
Unreal.
毫无疑问  难喝死了
Mm, and of course, it's gross.
好吧  那我把它拿走
Okay, well, I'll just take it back then.
不  用不着小题大做
No, no! No need to make a big deal out of things.
我就把它喝了吧
I'll just drink it.
你爸联系你了吗
Hey! Any word from your dad?
他大概两小时之前给我发的短信
He texted me, like, two hours ago.
我告诉他你加油的时候车没熄火
I told him how you kept the car running when you got gas
差点把我炸了
and could've blown me up.
你有没有跟他说那些有趣的事呢
But you told him about the fun things too right?
我们吃了那个超大饼干
We had that huge cookie,
你转身而去速度太快把头发甩到我嘴里
you spun away from me fast and got your hair in my mouth.
你拍照干嘛
What was that for?
我朋友贝特西有个图享帐号专门分享可悲的东西
My friend Betsy has an Insta about sad stuff.
-我不是在  -没事  我不会随意评判别人
- Oh, I-I wasn't... - No, it's okay. I don't judge.
我还涂了亮甲油呢
I'm wearing a clear coat on my nails.
我知道  真是个海汤大傻瓜
Yeah, I know, what a chowder head.
本意海鲜汤  波士顿名菜
既然说到地方美食
Hey, speaking of that regional delicacy...
我不会投票去波士顿的
I am not voting to go to Boston
就为了去看美国第一个食尸鬼[爱伦·坡]
just so we could see where America's first ghoul
他于1809年出生在波士顿
作品中常写到食尸鬼  吸血鬼  鬼魂之类的
是在那里学会如厕的
was potty trained.
介意把你咬掉我的头时
Care to wipe the lipstick off my neck
留下的口红印擦掉吗
from where you bit my head off?
为什么冰箱里没有橙汁
Hey -- And why is there no orange juice?
今天早上我妈才出门买了
My mom went out for some this morning.
真的吗
Really?
这你就觉得有趣了
That you find interesting?
我干脆现在就收拾准备去白痴海洋公园了吧
Might as well pack for SeaWorld right now.
各位  你们看到艾普丽了吗
Hey, guys, have you seen April?
刚还看到她的
Just saw her a minute ago.
她给我拍照
She had me pose
说要传到她朋友的一个图享帐号
for some Instagram thing her friend does.
你穿的这是什么
What is this?
-从不是大卖场的地方买来的衣服  -等会
- Clothes that don't come from a mall. - Hold on, hold on.
我应该看着你的
I'm supposed to be watching you.
我要去贝特西家
I'm going to Betsy's.
优步已经在外面等我了
My Uber's out front.
贝特西是谁
Who is this Betsy?
她父母在家吗
Are her parents even home?
你才只有14岁  你不能打优步出门
And you're 14. You're not Ubering anywhere.
还有  你快把妆卸了
Also, you -- you can lose the makeup
你这样看着像个
because you look like a prostitute
电子产品大会上的妓女
at an electronics convention.
立刻脱了它  然后去帮忙摆餐桌
Now, go wipe it off and help set the table.
怎么了  我还不习惯这样管教人  好吗
What? I'm -- I'm not used to being all parenty, okay?
不  你做得很好
No, you did a great job.
谢谢
Oh, thanks.
你刚站在那我觉得怪怪的
I just felt weird 'cause you were standing right there,
因为你才是专家
and you're, like, the expert.
我才不是什么专家
Oh, I am hardly the expert.
我还是
I still...
还是有自己的问题要解决
I still have my own stuff to work on.
也许我不该说她像个妓女
Maybe I shouldn't have called her a prostitute?
你应该享受这种快感
You gotta have fun with it. Hm.
爸爸
Hey, dad.
对不起今天我对你说话很凶
I'm sorry that I barked at you today.
都是因为得为博览会下决策时
It's just with this whole Expo decision...
我就像个小女孩需要爸爸的帮助
...I hate feeling like a little girl
我讨厌这种感觉
that needs her daddy's help.
但我想  向在橱柜界摸爬滚打了
But I guess there's no harm in looking to the guy
25年的男神求助又不会少我一块肉  是吧
who's been knocking it out of the park for 25 years, right?
当然
Nope.
男神能给你的最好的建议就是
And the best advice that guy could give you is,
跟着直觉走
go with you gut...
因为你确实做得很好
'cause you're good at this.
谢谢
Thanks.
谢谢  我已经做了决定了
Thanks. And I -- and I have made a decision.
我会带着马特洪峰去
I'm going with the Matterhorn.
完了
Damn it.
看看我找到了谁
Look who I found!
谢天谢地
Ay, thank God!
我还是头一回这么开心见到她
This is the first time I'm so happy to see her.
赶紧把项圈拿下来  趁他还没...
Let's get this shock collar off before he gets...
伙计们
Hello, guys!
我的乖宝宝在这呢
There's my little baby.
你俩把这些拿进去
You two, take these in the house.
车里还有几袋  来搭把手
I've got a couple left in the trunk. A little help, buddy.
-在大门外面吗  -快来  菲尔
- Oh, on the other side of the gate? - Come on, Phil!
他们不能再绕回来拿吗
Couldn't they just circle back around?
-你说啥  -没啥
- Say what? - It's nothing.
好吧  你拿那袋
All right, take that.
额的亲娘嘞
Oh, mama!
你怎么回事  捡起来呀
What's wrong with you? Pick it up.
就是  捡吧  我这就捡
Yeah, let's do it. Let's pick it up.
你到底抽什么风
What the hell's the matter with you?
-你乱嚎什么呢  -我才没...
- Why are you making those sounds? - I don't think that's...
好吧  放进去之后再出来拿
All right, when you're done here,
这儿还有呢
come back 'cause there's more.
好的
Okie-doke.
这是什么
What the hell is that?
电击项圈吗
Is that a shock collar?
不知道  看我的惊讶[电击]脸就知道
I don't know, but this is a shocked face
我这辈子从没见过这种玩意儿
because I have never seen something like that in my life.
这么说是你买的了
So you obviously bought it.
我只是不想让斯黛拉跑到街上去
I just didn't want Stella to walk out in the street.
所以才要栓狗绳啊
That's what a leash is for!
你是个不称职的狗妈妈
You're a bad dog owner.
坏狗妈妈
Bad dog owner!
那项圈怎么会在你身上
Why did you have it?
我知道为什么
Well, I know why.
因为他们是一伙的
Yeah, because they're all working together.
又来了
Oh, here we go.
你们该听听他今天早上
You should've heard his paranoia this morning
是怎么对那几个俄罗斯租客疑神疑鬼的
about the -- the Russian renters?
多谢提醒  多谢你提起这事
Oh, I'm glad -- I'm glad you brought up the Russians
看我发现了啥
because look at what I found!
那是我的征服者特别雪茄
That's my El Conquistador Especial.
今早歌洛莉亚从我这拿的
Gloria took that from me this morning.
我猜
Oh, let me guess,
就在她出门买橙汁之前
right before she went out to buy orange juice...
-没错  -其实她并没有买
- That's right. - ...Except for she wasn't.
她和小卡去赶占屋者了
She was with Cam getting rid of the squatters
而我被他拖住了
while I was being stalled by that man!
他们帮我藏麋鹿了
They helped me hide a reindeer!
去年圣诞节的事吗
From a year ago?
鬼知道他们这样已经多久了
Who knows how long this has been going on.
他们私自合伙
Okay, they've been in cahoots,
互相掩护犯下的错事
covering up each other's mistakes
在我们有机会羞辱他们之前就瞒住了
before we've even had a chance to shame them.
你们几个
Since this little alliance
背着我们拉帮结派擅自做决定
made a decision to go behind our backs,
我们也要不带你们  自己做决定一次
maybe we should make a decision without them...
比如度假地点
Oh. ...Like where we're going on vacation.
什么  不行  绝对不行
What? No, por favor, no!
什么  不行  怎么可以这样
What? No! You can't do that.
姐喜欢  姐喜欢
I like it. I like it.
就这么定了  去投票吧
Let's do this. Let's go vote.
好  有了
Yep. We've got it.
好了  我们决定了
Okay. We've reached a decision.
鼓声起
Drum roll please.
凑合吧
Close enough.
我们全家要去
The family is going to...
意大利
...Italy!
好棒啊
Ah! Yes!
天呐  太棒了
Oh, my God! That's awesome!
真好啊  大家
That's so awesome, guys!
最可笑的是他们还以为这主意是自己想出来的呢
The cutest part is that they think it was their idea.
在做什么呢
Mmm, what are you making?
是一道杰妈妈
I'm making an Italian dish
以前做过的意大利菜
that Jay's mother used to make.
意大利千层面早餐
Breakfast lasagna.
很棒的决定  亲爱的
Great call, honey.
亲爱的  你的早餐在桌上了
Hey, sweetie, your breakfast is on the table.
这是啥
Oh, what's this?
我给意大利帅哥取了名  他叫乔瓦尼
Oh! I've named him. It's Giovanni.
我还在想昨晚的电影
I'm still thinking about that movie last night.
你选得真是好
You picked a good one.
只有意大利人才拍得出这么浪漫的东西
Only the Italians could make something that romantic.
给我的爱人[意语]的煎饼
Flapjacks for mi amore.
谢谢[意语]
Oh, grazie.
爸  无意冒犯  这些杂志里的内容
No offense, dad, but I'm not sure these magazines
没你想的那么有价值
are the treasure trove of information you thought they were.
为什么这么说
What are you talking about?
《冰川:  直到永远》
Glaciers: Now and Forever.
《加拿大:  我们北方的神秘邻国》
Canada: Our mysterious Neighbor to the North.
这些失落部落的照片挺有意思的
Don't hate these photos of the lost tribes.
她裙子上吊的是人头
That's a human head hanging off her skirt.
孩子们  这些杂志记录的是
Kids, these magazines harken back to a time
人类为填饱肚子费尽心思的时代
when man had to forage and fight for his foods.
你们现在的日子过得太舒服了
You guys have it too easy nowadays.
可以躺着吃零食  说一句
You can lay around eating snacks saying,
"谷歌  把厨房灯调暗"就行了
"Okay, Google, dim the kitchen lights."
没问题
Sure thing.
继续  爸
Go ahead, Dad.
好吧  谷歌
Okay, Google,
给我放一段
show me a video of a kangaroo
袋鼠和海盗打羽毛球的片子
playing badminton with a pirate.
好的  正在在线播放
Sure, playing on YouTube.
太神了吧
What?